[
  {"question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡´", "response": "Bolivia"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡ª", "response": "Peru"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·", "response": "Argentina"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡º", "response": "Australia"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¦", "response": "Spain"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¦", "response": "Canada"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡ª", "response": "Germany"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹", "response": "Portugal"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡º", "response": "Russia"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡±", "response": "Chile"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡¹", "response": "Guatemala"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡³", "response": "China"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡µ", "response": "Japan"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡ª", "response": "Germany"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡º", "response": "Cuba"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡·", "response": "Puerto Rico"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡·", "response": "Brazil"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "response": "Ukraine"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¦", "response": "Panama"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹", "response": "Italy"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¨", "response": "Ecuador"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡»ğŸ‡ª", "response": "Venezuela"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡´", "response": "Colombia"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡½", "response": "Mexico"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡³", "response": "India"}, 
  {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¾", "response": "Paraguay"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡¬", "response": "Nigeria"}
]